Guide to the Martha Wilson Papers, 1950-2019 (bulk 1964-2006) MSS.175
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Correspondence, 1964-2013; 172383
  - Subseries A: General Correspondence, 190087
    - Ame, date illegible; 204059 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - American Association of Museums, 1986; 204060 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - American Civil Liberties Union Censorship Project, 1991; 204061 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - American Civil Liberties Union newsletter, 1992; 204062 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - The American Federation of Arts/ Mi Jin Hong, 1998; 204063 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - America's Funniest Home Videos, 1990; 204064 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Aminoff, Tania, 1978-2000; 204065 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Amos, Emma, 1995; 204066 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Amy and Mike, 2001; 204067 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Anastasia, 2006; 204068 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Amy and Fred, undated; 204069 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Anderson, Ally and Jack Spivy, 1989-1998; 204070 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Anderson, David, undated; 204071 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Anderson, Laurie, 1987-1998; 204072 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Anderson, Max and Jacqueline, undated; 204073 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Anderson, Maxwell, 2000; 204074 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Androccio, Carol, 1981; 204075 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Angelopoulos, Elaine, 2008; 204076 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Andy and Scott, 1980; 204077 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Ann, 1989; 204078 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Anna Leonowen's Gallery, 1995; 204079 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Anne, 1996; 204080 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Anne, 1999; 204081 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Anne, 2002; 204082 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Anne, undated; 204083 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Anne and Gretchen, undated; 204084 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Annie, 1975; 204085 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Annie, 1998; 204086 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Annie, undated; 204087 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Annie, Ana, Barbara, Barbara L., Garrisen, Lynn, Matthew A., [1982]; 204088 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - Annie and Jonathon, 1990; 204089 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - Anton, 1985; 204090 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - Antonacci, Lori/ Artists Talk in Art Inc., 1979; 204091 (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - Antupit, Samuel/Common Place Books, 1996; 204092 (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - Apple, Billy, 1975; 204093 (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - Apple, Jacki, 1986-2001 and undated; 204094 (Box 7, Folder 69)
    - April, 1979; 204095 (Box 7, Folder 70)
    - Aptekarm, Ken, 1994; 204096 (Box 7, Folder 71)
    - Armajani, Siah, undated; 204097 (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - Armand Hammer Museum/Sexual Politics, 1995-1996; 204098 (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - Arn, 1964-1965; 204099 (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - Arndt, Dianne, 1986-1987; 204100 (Box 7, Folder 74)
    - Arnoult, Philip, 1996; 204101 (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - [Arnplausen], Carol, 1981; 204102 (Box 7, Folder 76)
    - Arneson, Heidi, 1997; 204103 (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - Art Deadlines List, 2001; 204104 (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - Art Dealers Association of America, 1992; 204105 (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - Art Hazards News, 1986-1988; 204106 (Box 7, Folder 80)
    - Art Lab Inc. /Megan Pringle, 2004; 204107 (Box 7, Folder 81)
    - Art Matters, 1995; 204108 (Box 7, Folder 82)
    - Art Metropole, 2007; 204109 (Box 7, Folder 83)
    - Art Table, 1993; 204110 (Box 7, Folder 84)
    - Artists in Residence Gallery, 1983-2007; 204111 (Box 7, Folder 85)
    - Arts Coalition for Freedom of Expression, 1990; 204112 (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - Aru, 1964; 204113 (Box 7, Folder 87)
    - Ashley, George, 1984; 204114 (Box 7, Folder 89)
    - Asian Cine Vision/ Arlene Goldberg, 2002; 204115 (Box 7, Folder 90)
    - [Askevold], 1988; 204116 (Box 7, Folder 91)
    - Askevold, David, date illegible; 204117 (Box 7, Folder 92)
    - Astrid, Roland, Rosemary, 1986; 204118 (Box 7, Folder 93)
    - Athena [Tacha], 1977; 204119 (Box 7, Folder 94)
    - Atkins, Robert, 2003; 204120 (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - Atkinson, Esther, 1985; 204121 (Box 7, Folder 96)
    - Atkinson, Karen, 2007; 204122 (Box 7, Folder 97)
    - Augustmoon, Ochiishi, 1982-2001; 204123 (Box 7, Folder 98)
    - Aunt Belle, undated; 204124 (Box 7, Folder 99)
    - Aunt Mary, undated; 204125 (Box 7, Folder 100)
    - Avocus Publishing/Jennfer Peters, 1991-1992; 204126 (Box 7, Folder 101)
    - Aycock, Alice, 1975; 204127 (Box 7, Folder 102)
    - Aycock/ Segal, 1976; 204128 (Box 7, Folder 102)
    - Ayers, Robert, 2002; 204129 (Box 7, Folder 104)
    - B., 1986; 204130 (Box 7, Folder 105)
    - B., 1990; 204131 (Box 7, Folder 106)
    - B., 2001; 204132 (Box 7, Folder 107)
    - B.B., 1991; 204133 (Box 7, Folder 108)
    - B.B. and Lul, 1977; 204134 (Box 7, Folder 109)
    - B., Judy, undated; 204135 (Box 7, Folder 110)
    - B.K., undated; 204137 (Box 7, Folder 111)
    - B., Linda, 1987; 204136 (Box 7, Folder 112)
    - Bacon, Karin, 1986; 204138 (Box 7, Folder 113)
    - Baer, Josh, 1995; 204139 (Box 7, Folder 114)
    - Baker, Bill, undated; 204140 (Box 7, Folder 115)
    - Baker, Julia, 2001; 204141 (Box 7, Folder 116)
    - Baldely-Pörschman, Sandra and Dirk, 2002; 204142 (Box 7, Folder 117)
    - Baldessari, Mike Fink, 1976; 204143 (Box 7, Folder 118)
    - Balderston, Julia (Aunt Julia), 1975-1984; 204144 (Box 7, Folder 119)
    - Baldwin, Ann and Crans, 2003; 204145 (Box 7, Folder 120)
    - Ball, Lillian, 1991; 204146 (Box 7, Folder 121)
    - Bamberg-Johnson, Matthew, 2005; 204147 (Box 7, Folder 122)
    - Bandman, Murray, 1992; 204148 (Box 7, Folder 123)
    - The Banff Center, 1999; 204192 (Box 7, Folder 124)
    - Bankowsky, Jack, Charles Guarino and Knight Landesman, 1999; 204193 (Box 7, Folder 125)
    - Bannerman, Isabella, 1994; 204194 (Box 7, Folder 126)
    - Barbara, 1975; 204195 (Box 7, Folder 127)
    - Barbara, 1986-1989; 204196 (Box 7, Folder 128)
    - Barbara, 1995; 204197 (Box 7, Folder 129)
    - Barbara, undated; 204200 (Box 7, Folder 130)
    - Barbara, undated; 204201 (Box 7, Folder 131)
    - Barbara and her boys, 1988; 204202 (Box 7, Folder 132)
    - Barbara and Susan, undated; 204203 (Box 7, Folder 133)
    - Barbiere, Patrick, Mary Taylor and Deirdre Scharffs, 204204 (Box 7, Folder 134)
    - Bard College/Rhea Anastas, 204205 (Box 7, Folder 135)
    - Bard, Perry, 2002; 204206 (Box 7, Folder 136)
    - Barfield, Tanya, 1996; 204207 (Box 7, Folder 137)
    - Barowitz, Jane and Anne Richter/ Foundation for the Community of Artists, 1980; 204208 (Box 7, Folder 138)
    - Barnet-Sanchez, Holly, 2007-2008, undated; 204209 (Box 7, Folder 139)
    - Barrett, Deirdre/CAA, 2002-2007; 204210 (Box 7, Folder 140)
    - Barrett/Gosin, 1990; 204211 (Box 7, Folder 141)
    - Barron, Susan, 1985-2001; 204212 (Box 7, Folder 142)
    - Barry, 1996; 204213 (Box 7, Folder 143)
    - Barry, undated; 204215 (Box 7, Folder 144)
    - Barth, Bob, undated; 204216 (Box 7, Folder 145)
    - Bartlett, Jennifer, 1977; 204217 (Box 7, Folder 146)
    - Barton, Priscilla, 1988-1995; 204218 (Box 7, Folder 147)
    - Bartha, Catherine, 2005; 204219 (Box 7, Folder 148)
    - Baruch College, 2000; 204220 (Box 7, Folder 149)
    - Bascove, 1990; 204221 (Box 7, Folder 150)
    - Bastis, Kathleen, Merrry and Rad Pavelic, undated; 204222 (Box 7, Folder 151)
    - Batson, Bill, 2006; 204223 (Box 7, Folder 152)
    - Bay Area Video Coalition/ Kim Wood, 1997; 204224 (Box 7, Folder 153)
    - Bayer, Patricia, 1998; 204225 (Box 7, Folder 154)
    - Beatrice, 1998; 204226 (Box 7, Folder 155)
    - Beatty, Maria, 1991; 204227 (Box 7, Folder 156)
    - Beaumont, Betty, 1998-1999, undated; 204228 (Box 7, Folder 157)
    - Becker, Emmanuelle and Valtors Lindbergs, 1990; 204229 (Box 7, Folder 158)
    - Becky, 1982-1995; 204230 (Box 7, Folder 159)
    - Beebe, Aaron/Coney Island Museum, 2005; 204231 (Box 7, Folder 160)
    - Beigle, Lauren, undated; 204232 (Box 7, Folder 161)
    - Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library, 1987; 204233 (Box 7, Folder 162)
    - Beirne, Bill, 1976; 204234 (Box 7, Folder 163)
    - Belt, Mike, 1977; 204235 (Box 7, Folder 164)
    - Ben, Emily and Sarah, undated; 204236 (Box 7, Folder 165)
    - Ben-Haim, Tsipi, 2008; 204237 (Box 7, Folder 166)
    - Benitez, Sylvia, 1997-2000; 204238 (Box 7, Folder 167)
    - Bennington College/ Elissa Tenny, 2005; 204239 (Box 7, Folder 168)
    - Benrabia, Sabrina, 2000; 204240 (Box 7, Folder 169)
    - Benson, Vickie, 1998; 204241 (Box 7, Folder 170)
    - Berge, Carol, 1975; 204242 (Box 7, Folder 171)
    - [Berger], Ted, 1989, undated; 204243 (Box 7, Folder 172)
    - Berger, Theodore and Riger Bruce/New York Foundation for the Arts, 1985-2001; 204244 (Box 7, Folder 173)
    - Berghash, Mark, 1986-1995, undated; 204245 (Box 7, Folder 174)
    - Berghash, Mark W. and Rachel, 1983-1998, undated; 204246 (Box 7, Folder 175)
    - Berkowitz, Terry, 2000; 204255 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Berman, Jennifer/Bomb Magazine, 1996; 204256 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Bernstein, Judith, 1983-2008; 204257 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Berry, Carolyn, 1989; 204258 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Berry, Michael, 1980; 204259 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Bertlmann, Renate, 204260 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Betsalel, Ken/ UNCA, 1992; 204261 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Betsey, 1996; 204262 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Betty and Paul, undated; 204263 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Beube, Douglas, 1992-2001; 204264 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - BEZERK productions/Linda Sibio, 2001-2005, undated; 204265 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Bill, 1982-1985; 204266 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Bill, 1984; 204267 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Bill and Layne, 1988; 204268 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Bilsky, Pauline, undated; 204269 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Blachly, Jimbo, 2002; 204270 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Blake, Nathan, 1998; 204271 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Blanka, undated; 204272 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Blieden, Molly, 1998-2008, undated; 204273 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Blittner, Mr. and Mrs. Adam, 2005; 204274 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Bloch, Mark, 1985; 204275 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Block, Holly/ National Association of Artists Organizations, 1991-1994; 204276 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Block, Holly/ Art in General, 1991-1992, undated; 204277 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Block, Holly/ Art Table, 1998; 204278 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Blog Family, 1994-2004, undated; 204279 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Bloom, Barbara, 2002; 204280 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Bloom, Naomi Dagan, 2002; 204281 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - The Blue Noses, 2004; 204298 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Bluestone, Mimi and Herb Perr, 1991; 204299 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Blumberg, Eric, 1993; 204300 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Bob, 1998; 204301 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Bob and Olive, 1979; 204302 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Bokaer, Jonah, 2007; 204303 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Bolt, Macyn, 1991-1996; 204304 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Bonnie, 1977; 204305 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Bonnie, undated; 204306 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Bonnie and Ted, undated; 204307 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Book, Lynn, 2007; 204308 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Boone, John and Jenny, 1990-1998, undated; 204309 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Boothe, Power, 1976-2002, undated; 204310 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - [Borus], Janet, 1997; 204311 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - The Boss Family, 2003; 204312 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Bostric, Connie, 1995; 204313 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Bourgois, Patty, 1999; 204774 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Bowman, Robert, 1968; 204775 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Boyle, Kevin and Susan, 1976; Undated; 204776 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Brad, 1992; 204777 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Brad, 1996; 204778 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Brad, Undated; 204779 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Bradley, Sarah / Asian Cultural Council, 1995; 204780 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Brakely, Theresa, 1975; 204781 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Branch, Brenda René, 1997-2008; Undated; 204782 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Braunstein, Jerry H., 1978; 204783 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Brazil, Pat, 1998; 204784 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Brehm, Kate, 2006; 204785 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Brendan, Undated; 204786 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Brenda, 1998; 204787 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Brill, Amy, 1998; 204788 (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Britton, Susan, 1979-2000; 204789 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Brockman, Brad, 1994-2004; Undated; 204790 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Brodsky, Judy, 1996-2003; 204791 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Brohddus, John Eric, Undated; 204792 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Bronson, A.A., 2008; 204793 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - Brooklyn Arts Council / Carol Sterling, 2005; 204794 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Brooklyn Friends School, 2000; 204795 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - Brooklyn Historical Society / Deborah Schwartz, 2008; 204796 (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - Brooklyn Monthly Meeting, 1997-1999; 204797 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - Brooks, Yvonne, 2005; 204798 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - Brown, Melody, 1991; 204799 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - Brown, Nancy, 1979; 204800 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - Brown, Robert Delford, 1976-1984; 204801 (Box 8, Folder 70)
    - Bruce, Rodger / Jed Berger, Undated; 204802 (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - Brunner, Helen Mary / Donald Hayes Russell, 1989; 204803 (Box 8, Folder 72)
    - Bruno, Joseph, 2005; 204804 (Box 8, Folder 73)
    - Bruns, Anne, 1998-2001; Undated; 204805 (Box 8, Folder 74)
    - Bruns, Eileen, 1998-2005; 204806 (Box 8, Folder 75)
    - Bruns, Eileen and Christine, 1995-2006; Undated; 204807 (Box 8, Folder 76)
    - Bruns, Gustav and Anne, 1996-2000; Undated; 204808 (Box 8, Folder 77)
    - Bruns, Vince (also contains materials from Wilson), Undated; 204809 (Box 8, Folder 78)
    - Büchler, Pavel, 1989-1994; Undated; 204810 (Box 8, Folder 79)
    - Büchler, Alexandra and Pavel, 1996-1998; 204811 (Box 8, Folder 80)
    - Büchler, Alexandra and Pavel, 1999; 204812 (Box 8, Folder 81)
    - Buckley, Brad, 1986; 204813 (Box 8, Folder 82)
    - Budney, Jen, 1998; Undated; 204814 (Box 8, Folder 83)
    - Building Mates, 2002; 204815 (Box 8, Folder 84)
    - Bunning, Emily / Treehouse Shakers, 2007; 204816 (Box 8, Folder 85)
    - Burdick, Karen, 1978; 204817 (Box 8, Folder 86)
    - Buren, Daniel, 1988; 204818 (Box 8, Folder 87)
    - Burgoyne, Diana, 2007; 204819 (Box 8, Folder 88)
    - Burkey, Wayne, 1984; 204820 (Box 8, Folder 89)
    - Burnham, Linda, 1984-1986; 204821 (Box 8, Folder 90)
    - Burson, Nancy, 1990-2000; 204822 (Box 8, Folder 91)
    - Bush Foundation / Sally Dixon, 1991-2006; 204823 (Box 8, Folder 92)
    - Butler, Connie, 2005; 204824 (Box 8, Folder 93)
    - Butler, Ken, 2002; 204825 (Box 8, Folder 94)
    - Buzz, 1982; 204826 (Box 8, Folder 95)
    - C, 1992; 204827 (Box 8, Folder 96)
    - C, 1993; 204828 (Box 8, Folder 97)
    - C [Cecil] / Fordham, 2007; 204829 (Box 8, Folder 98)
    - Callard, Andrea; Matthew Geller, 1991; 204830 (Box 8, Folder 99)
    - Calvin and Patty, Undated; 204831 (Box 8, Folder 100)
    - Camp Onas, 1999-2001; Undated; 204832 (Box 8, Folder 101)
    - Campbell, Barbara, Undated; 204833 (Box 8, Folder 102)
    - Campbell, Pamela and Wanda, 1978; 204834 (Box 8, Folder 103)
    - Candace, 1996; 204835 (Box 8, Folder 104)
    - Canley, J., Undated; 204836 (Box 8, Folder 105)
    - Canna, Evan, Mike, Ryann, Undated; 204837 (Box 8, Folder 106)
    - Carboni, Gaetano, 2006; Undated; 204838 (Box 8, Folder 107)
    - Carey and Michelle, Undated; 204839 (Box 8, Folder 108)
    - Carl and Jacquelyn, Undated; 204840 (Box 8, Folder 109)
    - Carla and Noel, 1975; 204841 (Box 8, Folder 110)
    - Carlini, John; Ben Coleman, Undated; 204842 (Box 8, Folder 111)
    - Carlson, Moriah, 2001; 204843 (Box 8, Folder 112)
    - Carmical, Lee, Undated; 204844 (Box 8, Folder 113)
    - Carol, 1973; 204845 (Box 8, Folder 114)
    - Carol, 1988; 204846 (Box 8, Folder 115)
    - Carol, Undated; 204847 (Box 8, Folder 116)
    - Carol, Undated; 204848 (Box 8, Folder 117)
    - Carp, Alexis Smith, 1976; 204849 (Box 8, Folder 118)
    - Carpenter, Mary, 2005; 204850 (Box 8, Folder 119)
    - Carr, Cynthia, 2004-2006; 204851 (Box 8, Folder 120)
    - Carr, Robert; Theresa Tedesco, 1991; 204852 (Box 8, Folder 121)
    - Carrie, 2002; 204853 (Box 8, Folder 122)
    - Carrie, 2005; 204854 (Box 8, Folder 123)
    - Carsch, Ruth, 1983-1995; 204855 (Box 8, Folder 124)
    - Carter, Azure and Alan, 2001-2006; Undated; 204856 (Box 8, Folder 125)
    - Carulli, Diana, 1984; 204857 (Box 8, Folder 126)
    - Casa de las Americas - Gonzalo Domingo Cabrera, 1997; 204858 (Box 8, Folder 127)
    - Casey, Caroline, 1982-1985; 204859 (Box 8, Folder 128)
    - Catalyst Arts, 1995; 204860 (Box 8, Folder 129)
    - Catherine, Undated; 204861 (Box 8, Folder 130)
    - Cembalest, Robin / ArtForum, 1983; Undated; 204862 (Box 8, Folder 131)
    - Center, 1973; 204863 (Box 8, Folder 132)
    - The Center for Book Arts / Alexander Campos, 1994-2007; 204864 (Box 8, Folder 133)
    - Chalmers, Jessica, 2007; 204865 (Box 8, Folder 134)
    - Chamberlain, Mark; Rebecca Sherman, 1981-2006; 204866 (Box 8, Folder 135)
    - Chamberlain, Rebecca and Mark, 1996; Undated; 204867 (Box 8, Folder 136)
    - Chambers, Bruce / F.I.T., 1996; 204868 (Box 8, Folder 137)
    - Chambers, Bruce / F.I.T., 1996; 204869 (Box 8, Folder 138)
    - Champagne, Lenora, 1983-2003; Undated; 204870 (Box 8, Folder 139)
    - Channon, David, Undated; 204871 (Box 8, Folder 140)
    - Chao, Anita, 1997; 204872 (Box 8, Folder 141)
    - Chapman, Tim, 2003; 204927 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Char and Hannah, Undated; 204928 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Charlie, Undated; 204929 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Charlotte and Penny, Undated; 204930 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Chase, Kasem, 1973; 204931 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Chelsea Chiropractic, 1990-1993; 204932 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Chez Bushwick, 2007; 204933 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Chinaberry Books, 1991; 204934 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Chou, Jerome / The New Press, 1995; 204935 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Chrissie, Illegible; 204936 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Christa and [Jill], 1978; 204937 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Christian, 1995; 204938 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - [Christon], Alice, Undated; 204939 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Chris, Cynthia / Printed Matter, 1995-1996; 204940 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Christov, Alice; George Moore / Intercambios Culturales of El Salvador, 1995-1996; 204941 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Christov; Moore, 1998; 204942 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Chunn, Nancy, Undated; 204943 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Cindy, 1979; 204944 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Circle of Gold, Undated; 204945 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Claire, Undated; 204946 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Claire, 1989; 204947 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Clarke, John P., 1986; 204948 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Clarke, Elly, 2002; 204949 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Claus and Ariane, Undated; 204950 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Clinton, Bill (Democratic National Convention), Undated; 204951 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Cloud, Lea, 2005; 204952 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Clough, Charles, 1972; 204953 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - CNN / Gail Evans, 1992; 204954 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Coates, Brenda, 1993; 204955 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Cockburn Family, 1998; 204956 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Cockburn, Stormie [and girls], 1997; 204957 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Coco, 1986; 204958 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Cody, Steven / Ski Windam, 1994; 204959 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Coggeshall, Agnes W., 1980-1981; 204960 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Cognita, N. Vernita, 1995; 204961 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Cohen, Charles / University of Chicago, 2005; 204962 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Cohen, Elaine Lustig, Undated; 204963 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Cohen, Norma, 1995; 204964 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Cohen, Ruth, 1988; 204965 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Coleman, Anna, 2000; 204966 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Coleman, Grisha, Undated; 204967 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Coleman, Mimsie, 1990-1991; 204968 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Colleen, 1984; 204969 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Colleen and Chris, 1977; 204970 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - College Art Association / Mary-Beth Shine, 1992-1999; 204971 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Colmer, Roy, 2006-2007; 204972 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Colo, Papo and Jeanette Ingberman, 1991; 204973 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Colombatto, Perhi, 1991, undated; 204974 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Comfort Family, 1995-1996; 204975 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Connor, Maureen, 2001; 204976 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Contento/O'Malley, undated; 204977 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Con Edison, 1975; 204978 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Contemporary Art Institute of Detroit, undated; 204979 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Conwill, Kinshasha, 2001; 204989 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Cook, Richard and Doris, 1990-1994; 204990 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Cook, Scott, 1988-2005; 204991 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Cook, Scott, 1985-1986, undated; 204992 (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Cook, Susana, 2001-2002, undated; 204993 (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Cook-Wilson, Comley, 1997-2003, undated; 204994 (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Cooper-Henry, Adjowii, 1999; 204995 (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Copp, Fletcher, 1996, undated; 204996 (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - [Corin] Nina, 1987; 204997 (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - Corlin, Kelli, undated; 204998 (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - Coro Foundation/ Andrew Rubinson, 1992; 204999 (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - Correspondence from Martha, no address, undated; 205000 (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - Correspondence neither to nor from Wilson, 1986, 1991, undated; 205001 (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - Cortigan, Steven, 1977; 205002 (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - Constanzo, Jim/RePo History, 2001; 205003 (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - Constantino, Roselyn, 1999; 205004 (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - Costello, Terence, undated; 205005 (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - Cottingham, Laura, 1994-2007; 205006 (Box 9, Folder 70)
    - Coulson, Anthony J., 1992; 205007 (Box 9, Folder 71)
    - Covan, Ellie/Dixon Place, 1991-2006, undated; 205008 (Box 9, Folder 72)
    - Ellie [Covan] and [Lauren], undated; 205010 (Box 9, Folder 73)
    - Cowboy John, Spider Webb, Phil Jonns, 1979; 205012 (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - Coyne, Petah, 1993-2001; 205013 (Box 9, Folder 75)
    - Cramer, Erin, 1989; 205014 (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - Crandall, Jordan/ X-Art Foundation, 1993; 205015 (Box 9, Folder 77)
    - Crane, Mike, 205016 (Box 9, Folder 78)
    - Crash, undated; 205017 (Box 9, Folder 79)
    - Crawford, Cair, 1998; 205018 (Box 9, Folder 80)
    - Crawford, Frank, 1965; 205019 (Box 9, Folder 81)
    - Creative Time, 1993-1998; 205020 (Box 9, Folder 82)
    - Crest, William, 1985; 205021 (Box 9, Folder 83)
    - Croll-Smith, Caroline, 1984; 205022 (Box 9, Folder 84)
    - Cronin, Ciara/ James O'Malley P.C., 2005; 205023 (Box 9, Folder 85)
    - Cronin, Kelly/ Wayne State, 1989; 205024 (Box 9, Folder 86)
    - Cross Section Exhibition/ Marcella Steingart, 1992; 205025 (Box 9, Folder 87)
    - Crotty, James, 2006; 205026 (Box 9, Folder 88)
    - Crowly, Mary, undated; 205027 (Box 9, Folder 89)
    - Crowne, Melchia, 1987-1991, undated; 205028 (Box 9, Folder 90)
    - Culkin, Jody, 1988-1997, undated; 205029 (Box 9, Folder 91)
    - Cullen, Kathleen and Denis Ray, 1987; 205030 (Box 9, Folder 92)
    - Cullen, Deborah, 2007; 205031 (Box 9, Folder 93)
    - R. Cumming, undated; 205032 (Box 9, Folder 94)
    - Cummings, Linda, 1993-1995; 205033 (Box 9, Folder 95)
    - Cunningham, Elena, 1997; 205034 (Box 9, Folder 96)
    - Curmano, Billy, 1994-2000; 205035 (Box 9, Folder 97)
    - Cushmore, Edna and Larry, 1967-2001, undated; 205036 (Box 9, Folder 98)
    - Cutforth, Roger, undated; 205037 (Box 9, Folder 99)
    - Cypis, Dorit, 1976-1985; 205038 (Box 9, Folder 100)
    - Cypis. Dorit with enclosure (wrapped in paper), 1979; 205319 (Box 9, Folder 101)
    - D, 2002; 205320 (Box 9, Folder 102)
    - D (vg), undated; 205321 (Box 9, Folder 103)
    - D [Dlier], 2001; 205322 (Box 9, Folder 104)
    - D, L, O, 1989; 205323 (Box 9, Folder 105)
    - D + M, 1992; 205324 (Box 9, Folder 106)
    - D'Amato, Alfonse, 1983; 205325 (Box 9, Folder 107)
    - D'arc, Victor and Mary Lee, 1976; 205326 (Box 9, Folder 108)
    - DaDao Live Art Festival/ Shu Yang, 2006; 205327 (Box 9, Folder 109)